



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Empathetic and collaborative problem solver with a genuine curiosity to truly understand and help others. As a designer, I always find myself asking Why, How Might We, and Does this experience solve the needs of the user. I am excited to bring my full stack UX experience and a unique global perspective to an organization that is poised and moving towards solving global challenges with technology.

EXPERIENCE

Design Work March 2017 - Current

- Led a 4 person team in designing the digital layout, typography, graphics, and logo for a non-profit client
- Designed an online and print advertisement for real estate firm resulting in 400 additional leads
- Created visual designs for a non-profit fundraising event that garnered over \$60K in donations

NAVICENT HEALTH September 2009 - September 2011 Macon, GA Administrative Assistant to VP

- Managed \$500K payroll process for 5 Directors and maintained \$20K travel budget for 10 members.
- Coordinated w/12 member IT and L&D team to create an application system that tracked medical staff certifications ensuring data migration and 100% state compliance w/in 3 months
- FMLA advisor for a 300 member staff; informed people of legal rights and protections and connecting them with HR representative.
- Revamped filing system by authoring the security and compliance measures to remove sensitive PII, enforce federal compliance, and ensure data accuracy for 2K documents.
- Coordinated with Vendors, travel, HR, and maintainedoffice supplies \$10k

THYSSENKRUPP ELEVATOR September 2008 - March 2009 Grand Rapids, MI Accounts Payable, Admin Asst.

- Managed +\$1M payroll process for +30 team of service technicians and construction technicians.
- Responsible for all accounts payable +\$100K.
- Created an application system that tracked all new construction jobs, listing their budget, PO's and information pertinent to each job.
- Performed accounting tasks such as submitting 10- 15 weekly check requests, and expense reports for the office and invoices.
- Coordinated and submitted all construction permits for new builds and remodles.
- Scheduled and tracked service calls, identifying which ones required immediate attention.

PROJECTS

CORE | Mobile and Web Application | View at christinabarker.com

Created as a multi-functional cloud storage desktop and iOS app that connects, organizes, and increases productivity for the customer. My role included research, stragegy, brand development,

BRIGHT | Mobile and Web Application | Currently in the research phase. Created to be a part of Google Classroom. This Android app will reinforce literacy skills.

EDUCATION

Bloc 2018 - 2019 Certificate UX Designer

Southern New Hampshire University

Online 2015 - 2018

BA, Graphic Design 3.5 GPA

Macon State University

Macon, GA 2008-2012
Business Administration

SKILLSTOOLS

Adobe Creative Suite
Figma
Sketch
Invision
Wire-framing
Prototyping

RESEARCH

User Interviews
Personas
User Stories
Usability Testing

DESIGN

Storyboards Mockups Prototyping

DEVELOPMENT

Terminal
Git/GitHub
HTML/CSS/
JavaScript/jQuery